This is the right opportunity in front of you, just to
welcome you. Hello Sanjeev ji, good day.
Tell me where are you tracking the momentum
today? Look at Mindtree's numbers,
top 10 money is moved into that, but I am still thinking about
bank control
rooms. I will tell you that whatever you say, Bank Nifty is going to reach 37,000,
whether it comes in 15 days or a
month, but I have friends in banks and there is a
lot more in midcap banks. The
commentary that has come today from Bandhan Bank and Mirch Matar
Microfinance says that landing is
dam recovery at 72825, cent and temples
and valid 98% stop Bandhan etc. I
request you to take the benefit of Bandhan,
you will be rewarded by midcap bank. Let me
give you an update on Rubaru Circle. I had given you 9350
anti-finance earlier, I did 95.50,
book profit in that and
you have two pics of making ₹2 handsome. Here I would
also like to tell you that I remembered the bank 1035 one, I
cut 1150.  It has become 1185
that probably micro finance law and urban
bank category under-21 team event today's 2
pictures if you say then I will start from the phone ji
machine so the first one came
ICICI Lombard Insurance from the ground
and Insurance Guddu Yadav stream
ICICI Lombard after getting 1658
character 215 346 take it in 1540 the stoploss is 1510 12
this is going back to
sixteen Hazelwood is also my favorite updates
UP Bank of Baroda Bank of Baroda will
give the highest record profit in this quarter
which is your July end episode 220
take it in eighty-four and a half but stop loss 7250
decided to ₹90 ok so Bank of Baroda SA
number of sciences on ambulance packing
machine safa today's hot topic of discussion
in the new year is
what has happened in the IPO of Metro, should we invest money in it
give its price for 7276 and then
trend more vigorously  He is telling this to
friends and friends that this
spa in its price is above fiction but this talk
will make money over the next few years
so figure out where it winds up and
used to give you are you written off just take it like this
sir no brainer as I told you
earlier there is no metric of its valuation so it is
difficult for us to comment but I think you must have this
in your portfolio in
small quantities